businessblueprint.com 2015-12-08

# Privacy Policy — Business Blueprint

Dream Express International Pty Ltd (ABN 21 115 281 420) trading as “Business Blueprint” (“ **we** ”, “us” or the “ **Company** ”) is committed to privacy protection. At http://businessblueprint.com (“ **Business Blueprint** ” or “ **this site** ”), we understand the importance of keeping personal information private and secure.

This privacy policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) describes generally how we manage personal information and safeguard privacy. If you would like more information, please don’t hesitate to contact us.

This Privacy Policy forms part of, and is subject to the provisions of, our Usage Terms.

**We care about your privacy:**

**We will never rent, trade or sell your email address to anyone.**

**We will never publicly display your email address or other personal details that identify you.**

## The National Privacy Principles

* * *

We are bound by the National Privacy Principles of Australia, as provided in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (“ **Privacy Act** ”). If you require any further information about the Privacy Act and the National Privacy Principles, you can visit the Federal Privacy Commissioner’s website (see www.privacy.gov.au).

## What is “personal information”?

* * *

Personal information held by the Company may include (without limitation) your:

  * name and date of birth;
  * residential and business addresses, telephone/mobile/fax numbers and email addresses;
  * bank account and/or credit card details for agreed billing purposes;
  * preferences for using this site as well as your computer and connection information; and 
  * any other personal information that you add to your Business Blueprint user profile or otherwise share with us.

## How we may collect your personal information

At Business Blueprint, we only collect personal information that is necessary for us to conduct our business (“ **Business** ”), which includes (without limitation):

  * online business and personal development education;
  * web-based streaming of live and recorded business and personal development training presentations;
  * providing other online business and personal development training resources across a range of different formats, including video, audio and written/graphical materials;
  * hosting of online forums for discussion of topics related to business and personal development education; and
  * facilitating live online business and personal development seminars, classes, tutorials and coaching sessions.

## Information that you provide to us

We may collect personal information that you provide to us about yourself when you:

use this site, including (without limitation) when you:

  * create a user account;
  * add information to your user profile;
  * register for access to premium content or request certain premium features;
  * purchase any goods or services through this site;
  * complete an online contact form to contact us or any of our affiliated training providers; or
  * add reviews, forum or chat room messages or comments in any elements of this site that permit user-generated content;
  * provide information to us by telephone or other means of telecommunication; and/or
  * send us an email or other written communication (eg, through our online contact form).

## IP addresses

This site may also collect Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. IP addresses are assigned to computers on the internet to uniquely identify them within the global network. Business Blueprint may collect IP addresses in order to provide internet session management and for security purposes. We may also collect and use web log, computer and connection information for security purposes and to help prevent and detect any misuse of, or fraudulent activities involving, this site.

## Cookies

* * *

## What is a cookie?

This site uses “cookies” to help personalise your online experience. A cookie is a text file or a packet of information that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server to identify and interact more effectively with your computer. There are two types of cookies that may be used at this site: a persistent cookie and a session cookie. A persistent cookie is entered by your web browser into a dedicated folder for cookies on your computer and remains in that folder after you close your browser, and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to this site. A session cookie is held temporarily in your computer’s memory and disappears after you close your browser or shut down your computer. Cookies cannot be used to run programs. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. In some cases, cookies may collect and store personal information about you. The Company extends the same privacy protection to your personal information, whether gathered via cookies or from other sources.

## Why we use cookies

This site uses cookies in order to:

  * manage the signup process when you create an account with us;
  * remember your preferences for using this site;
  * recognise you as logged in while you remain so. This avoids your having to log in again every time you visit a new page;
  * show relevant notifications to you (eg, notifications that are relevant only to users who have, or have not, created an account or subscribed to newsletters or email or other subscription services);
  * facilitate e-commerce transactions, to ensure that your order is remembered between pages during the checkout process; and
  * remember details of data that you choose to submit to us (eg, through online contact forms or by way of comments, forum posts, chat room messages, reviews, ratings, etc).
  * Many of these cookies are removed or cleared when you log out but some may remain so that your preferences are remembered for future sessions.

## Third party cookies

In some cases, third parties may place cookies through this site. For example:

  * Google Analytics, one of the most widespread and trusted website analytics solutions, may use cookies de-identified data about how long users spend on this site and the pages that they visit;
  * Google AdSense, one of the most widespread and trusted website advertising solutions, may use cookies to serve more relevant advertisements across the web and limit the number of times that a particular advertisement is shown to you; and
  * third party social media applications (eg, SproutSocial, Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Pinterest, YouTube, Instagram, etc) may use cookies in order to facilitate various social media buttons and/or plugins in this site.

## Your cookie settings

You can configure your internet browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies or notify you when a cookie is sent. Please refer to your internet browser’s instructions to learn more about these functions. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may break, disable or otherwise adversely affect the functionality of Business Blueprint and many other websites.

## How we may use your personal information

* * *

Your personal information may be used in order to:

  * deliver streamed live and recorded business and personal development training presentations, as well as other educational materials, to you as you may request through this site or any related mobile application;
  * process any purchases of goods and/or services that you may make through this site;
  * administer and manage any payments that may be made by you to the Company in respect of purchases for goods or services or otherwise, including charging, billing and collecting debts;
  * respond to any queries or feedback that you may have;
  * verify your identity and conduct appropriate checks for credit-worthiness and for fraud;
  * prevent and detect any misuse of, or fraudulent activities involving, this site;
  * conduct research and development in respect of our products and services;
  * gain an understanding of your information and communication needs or obtain your feedback or views about our products/services in order for us to improve them; and/or
  * maintain and develop our business systems and infrastructure, including testing and upgrading of these systems,
  * and for any other purpose reasonably considered necessary or desirable by the Company in relation to the operation of the Business.

From time to time we may email our customers with news, information and offers relating to our own products and services or those of selected partners. This is to keep you informed of products, services and special offers that we believe you will find valuable and may continue after you cease acquiring goods or services from us. If you would prefer not to receive promotional or other material from us, please let us know and we will respect your request. You can unsubscribe from such communications at any time if you so choose.

## When we may disclose your personal information

* * *

## Information provided to suppliers

When you acquire or access any other goods or services from a third party supplier through this site, we will provide to that supplier such information as is necessary to enable it to process and administer your order. Such information will include personal information about you, including (without limitation) your name and contact details.

## Information provided to other organisations

In order to deliver the products/services you require or for the purposes set out above, the Company may also disclose your personal information to other organisations outside the Company. Your personal information may be disclosed to these organisations only in relation to Business Blueprint, and the Company takes reasonable steps to ensure that these organisations are bound by confidentiality and privacy obligations in relation to the protection of your personal information. These organisations may carry out or provide:

  * customer enquiries;
  * mailing systems;
  * information technology services;
  * marketing, telemarketing and sales services;
  * market research; and
  * website usage analysis.
  * In addition, we may disclose your personal information to:
  * your authorised representatives or legal advisers (when requested by you to do so);
  * credit-reporting and fraud-checking agencies;
  * credit providers (for credit-related purposes such as checks for creditworthiness, credit rating as well as credit provision and financing);
  * banks or other financial institutions (for the purposes of processing payments made by you to the Company);
  * our professional advisers, including our accountants, auditors and lawyers;
  * government and regulatory authorities and other organisations, as required or authorised by law;
  * organisations who manage our business and corporate strategies, including those involved in a transfer/sale of all or part of our assets or business (including accounts and trade receivables) and those involved in managing our corporate risk and funding functions; and/or
  * the police or other appropriate persons where your communication suggests possible illegal activity or harm to others.

## Contacting us about privacy

* * *

If you would like more information about how we manage personal information that we may hold about you, or are concerned that we may have breached your privacy, please contact our Privacy Officer by email to support@businessblueprint.com.

## Access to your personal information

In most cases, you may have access to personal information that we hold about you. We will handle requests for access to your personal information in accordance with the National Privacy Principles of Australia. All requests for access to your personal information must be directed to our Privacy Officer by email using the email address provided above. We will deal with all requests for access to personal information as quickly as possible. Requests for a large amount of information, or information that is not currently in use, may require further time before a response can be given. We may charge you a fee for access if a cost is incurred by us in order to retrieve your information, but in no case will we charge you a fee for your application for access.

In some cases, we may refuse to give you access to personal information that we hold about you. This may include circumstances where giving you access would:

  * be unlawful (eg, where a record that contains personal information about you is subject to a claim for legal professional privilege by one of our contractual counterparties);
  * have an unreasonable impact on another person’s privacy; or
  * prejudice an investigation of unlawful activity.

We may also refuse access where the personal information relates to existing or anticipated legal proceedings, and the information would not be accessible by the process of discovery in those proceedings. If we refuse to give you access, we will provide you with reasons for our refusal.

## Correcting your personal information

We will amend any personal information about you that is held by us and that is inaccurate, incomplete or out of date if you request us to do so. If we disagree with your view about the accuracy, completeness or currency of a record of your personal information that is held by us, and you ask us to associate with that record a statement that you have a contrary view, we will take reasonable steps to do so.

## Storage and security of your personal information

* * *

We are committed to maintaining the confidentiality of the information that you provide us and we will take all reasonable precautions to protect your personal information from unauthorised use or alteration. In our business, personal information may be stored both electronically (on our computer systems and with our website hosting provider) and in hard-copy form. Firewalls, anti-virus software and email filters, as well as passwords, protect all of our electronic information. Likewise, we take all reasonable measures to ensure the security of hard-copy information. It is not possible, however, for us to guarantee the security of your personal information and the disclaimers and limitations of liability in our website usage terms also apply to any access of your personal information by a hacker or other unauthorised third party.

## Third party websites

* * *

You may click-through to third party websites from this site, in which case we recommend that you refer to the privacy statement of the third party websites that you visit. This Privacy Policy applies to this site only and the Company assumes no responsibility for the content of any third party websites.

## Re-marketing

We may use the Google AdWords and/or Facebook re-marketing services to advertise on third party websites to previous visitors to this site based upon their activity on this site. This allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and to only display advertisements that are relevant to you. Such advertising may be displayed on a Google search results page or a website in the Google Display Network or inside Facebook. Google and Facebook may use cookies and/or pixel tags to achieve this. Any data so collected by Google and/or Facebook will be used in accordance with their own respective privacy policies. None of your personal Google and/or Facebook information is reported to us.

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ads Settings page (https://www.google.com/settings/ads). Facebook has enabled an AdChoices link that enables you to opt out of targeted advertising and you can also click on the “x” in the upper-right-hand corner of any targeted Facebook advertisement to reveal further options.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

From time to time, it may be necessary for us to revise this Privacy Policy and we reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Any such changes will be in accordance with the Privacy Act and the National Privacy Principles of Australia. We may notify you about changes to this Privacy Policy by posting an updated version on this site.
